

David Fleshman

Graphic Designer, Photographer, and Illustrator 10426 Alpine Edge Avenue, Las Vegas, NV 89129 dforiginaldesignsllc@gmail.com | dforiginaldesignsllc.com | 702.287.0370

Summary:

Qualified Graphic Designer specializing in User Experience design, branding identity and marketing materials such as packaging design, bookmarks, and postcards. Highly artistic in traditional illustration (pencil, charcoal, ink, and paint), always completed projects on time and fluent in Adobe Creative Suite. Able to create eye-catching graphics, branding, and engaging designs.

Skills:

- Graphic and Media Design
- Branding and Identity
- High-End Photo Retouching
- Adobe XD
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Lightroom Classic
- Adobe After Effects
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Adobe Dreamweaver (HTML & CSS)

- Visual Communication
- Digital and Print
- Leadership

Technical Skills:

- WordPress
- Wix
- Autodesk Maya
- Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel. PowerPoint, Outlook)
- Traditional Illustration: (Graphite on Paper, Charcoal, Ink, Paint)

EXPERIENCE:

The 7th Magazine, Clermont, *Florida*

- Graphic Designer Intern

Jan 2021 -

Present

- Developed, designed, and produced variety of technical illustrations for magazines
- Created golden plated foil and golden leaf stamping.
- Used Adobe Photoshop to retouch and color correction high-end photographs of models.
- Realigned the Sweet SXM Beauty logo and banner along with creating a more appealing background for the makeup bottles and the makeup oil for the beauty line.

DF Original Designs L.L.C., Las Vegas, Nevada

Jun 2019 -

- Owner/Founder

Present

 Worked with clients such as Nevada State Museum, U.S. Medical Professionals L.L.C. and Quinn Design Studios performing freelance work as an Illustrator and Graphic Designer to enhance the clients marketing design packages.

Terrible Herbst Inc, Las Vegas, Nevada

Sep 2019 -

- Cashier

Mar 2020

- Welcoming customers, answering their questions, helping them locate items, provide advice or recommendations, processing exchange or refunds and resolving complaints.
- Cashiering duties include operating cash registers, assisting customers in the in-store check-out process, ringing up sales, bagging items, requesting price checks, honoring coupons and EBT cards, collecting payment and giving appropriate change.
- Maintain clean and orderly checkout area. Complete other general cleaning duties, such as mopping floors, emptying trash cans, stocking shelves and repricing labels on merchandise.
- Troubleshooting cashier computer
- · Possess Food Handlers Safety Training Card, Alcohol Awareness Training Card and Non-Gaming Card.

Nevada State Museum, Las Vegas, Nevada

Jun 2019 -

- Graphic Designer

Sep 2019

- Worked with clients to define their requirements and established scopes of the project.
- Used Adobe Photoshop and InDesign to create bookmarks and postcards.



David Fleshman

Graphic Designer, Photographer, and Illustrator 10426 Alpine Edge Avenue, Las Vegas, NV 89129 dforiginaldesignsllc@gmail.com | dforiginaldesignsllc.com | 702.287.0370

 Used Adobe Photoshop to retouch over 60 photographs along with dry photo mounting photographs for the Electric Nevada Exhibition https://www.lasvegasnvmuseum.org/exhibits/eclectic-nevada/

Mountain View Presbyterian Church, Las Vegas, Nevada

Sep 2013 -

Mar 2020

- Supervisor of all Audio and Visual Soundboard technicians
 - Performed various setups and tear downs of all audio equipment such as soundboard, speakers, microphones, and ear buds. Sound mixing for bands, concerts, weddings, funerals, worship services and theatrical performances.
 - Checked all technical equipment to make sure it was functioning properly and performed troubleshooting problems that come up during the service.
 - Transformed video and audio recordings into digital formats for editing and archiving including live streaming the church services on Facebook and YouTube with HD Cameras.

U.S. Medical Professionals L.L.C., Las Vegas, Nevada

Mar 2019 -

- Freelance Graphic Designer

Apr 2019

- Worked with the client to gather and define project requirements.
- Establish the scope of the project and managed a tight deadline to finish five packaging designs in three weeks
- Designed final touches for package design such as image sizing, typography and layout while using Adobe Illustrator and communicating with the client through email for any revisions.

Quinn Design Studios, Las Vegas, Nevada

Dec 2018 -

- Freelance Illustrator

Jan 2019

- Pencil & Charcoal Hand Drawn Portrait
- Worked with the client to understand the requirements and provide excellent service
- Applying color theory technique in each drawing to add excitement, focus and depth.

Mountain View Presbyterian Church, Las Vegas, Nevada

Jan 2009 -Sep 2013

Audio and Visual Soundboard Technician

- Certified A/V Soundboard Technician through Mountain View Presbyterian Church
- Technician of cameras, sound system, and PowerPoint presentations in Sanctuary
- Performed similar A/V soundboard tasks for numerous events in Fellowship Hall

NASCAR and Monster Jam Races Salesclerk

Mar 2007 -Mar 2015

Las Vegas Motor Speedway, Las Vegas, Nevada

- Seller of souvenir merchandise to 1,000s of event visitors
- Cashier, stock merchandiser, inventory, and accounting

Boy Scouts of America Las Vegas Area Council, Summer Camp, Mt. Potosi, Nevada Summer Camp Staff/Merit Badge Counselor

Jun 2010 -

July 2010

- Taught 60 boy scouts two handicraft merit badges which they all earned
- · Taught wood carving, leather tanning and basic first aid skills

EDUCATION:

University of Nevada, Las Vegas, Las Vegas, Nevada, GPA: 3.60

Aug 2015 -

Bachelor of Science in Graphic Design and Media

May 2018

- Minor Art History
- UX Design Research Brand Identity Web Design
- UNLV Capstone Graphic Design Thesis Exhibition called "spacesthethesis.design" (Defunct) facebook.com/spacesthethesis/
- UNLV Konami Student Work Brand Identity
- Phi Alpha Theta-Psi Sigma, History Honor Society Member and Webmaster

College of Southern Nevada, Las Vegas, Nevada, GPA: 3.60

Aug 2019 -

Associate of Arts Degree in Art

Dec 2019



David Fleshman

Graphic Designer, Photographer, and Illustrator 10426 Alpine Edge Avenue, Las Vegas, NV 89129 dforiginaldesignsllc@gmail.com | dforiginaldesignsllc.com | 702.287.0370

College of Southern Nevada , <i>Las Vegas, Nevada</i> , GPA: 3.60 Associate of Applied Science Degree in Graphic Technology - Computer Graphics Design	Aug 2009 - May 2014
College of Southern Nevada, Las Vegas, Nevada, GPA: 3.60 Certification in Graphic Communications – Graphic Design	Aug 2009 - Aug 2014
Southeast Career Technical Academy , Las Vegas, Nevada, GPA: 3.60 Major: Animation and Digital Game Development	Aug 2005 - June 2009
HONORS/AWARDS:	
15 th Annual AVA Digital Awards, Gold Winner, Case Study of Walmart 14 th Annual International Design Awards IDA 2020, Bronze Winner, Walmart Case Study 57 th Design Annual, 2020 GDUSA, American Graphic Design Award, Reflection of Oneself 17 th Annual MarCom Award, Platinum Winner, Case Study of Walmart University of Nevada, Las Vegas (UNLV) – Dean's Honor List and Scholarship Recipient University of Nevada, Las Vegas (UNLV) – Dean's Honor List and Scholarship Recipient University of Nevada, Las Vegas (UNLV) – Dean's Honor List and Scholarship Recipient University of Nevada, Las Vegas (UNLV) – Scholarship Recipient Cynthia Bunker/Joy McClenahan Scholarship Boy Scout of America Las Vegas Area Council (BSA) – Venturing Silver Award Nevada State Treasurer – The Governor Guinn Millennium Scholarship Boy Scout of America Las Vegas Area Council (BSA) – Eagle Scout Award North Star District BSA Las Vegas Area Council – Patch Design Contest Winner	Jan 2021 Dec 2020 Nov 2020 Nov 2020 2018 - 2019 2017 - 2018 2016 - 2017 2015 - 2016 Apr 2015 Mar 2011 Jun 2009 Apr 2008
DESIGN EXHIBITIONS:	
UNLV, Spaces Graphic Design Thesis Exhibition, Participant, <i>Las Vegas, NV</i> CSN 18 th Bi-Annual Graphic Art Exhibit & Portfolio Review, As a Judge, <i>Las Vegas, NV</i> CSN 10 th Bi-Annual Graphic Art Exhibit & Portfolio Review, As a Judge, <i>Las Vegas, NV</i> CSN 10 th Bi-Annual Graphic Art Exhibit & Portfolio Review, Participant, <i>Las Vegas, NV</i>	May 2018 Dec. 2017 Dec. 2014 May 2014
<u>ASSOCIATIONS</u>	
Phi Alpha Theta-Psi Sigma, History Honor Society – Webmaster & Member Golden Key, International Honor Society – Treasurer & Member Phi Sigma Pi, National Honor Fraternity Society – Member Phi Eta Sigma, National Honor Society – Member National Honor Society Organization – Member The National Society of Leadership and Success – Member AIGA (American Institute of Graphic Arts) – Member PTK (Phi-Theta Kappa) Honor Society – Member	Feb 2018 Feb 2018 Jan 2018 Feb 2017 Feb 2017 Sep 2016 Mar 2014 Sep 2011

References Available on Request